Guide to the The Nick Zedd Papers 1963 - 2010 MSS.311
Fales Library and Special Collections
- OVERSIZE Series VII: Objects, 215534
  - Subseries C: The Mexican Kit, 215557 (Box 18, Box 40, Box 41, Box 42, Box 43, Box 44, Box 47, Box 45, Box 46, Folder 10, Folder 13 Left)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0055)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0056)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0057)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0058)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 40, Object 311.2.0059)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0060)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0061)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0062)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0063)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0064)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0065)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0066)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0067)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0068)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0069)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0070)
    - [Sugar skull], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0071)
    - [Hello kitty bandages], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0072)
    - [Skull figurine white], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0073)
    - [Skull figurine black], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0074)
    - [Cheetah mask wrestler], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0075)
    - [White, black, and red mask wrestler], undated (Box 41, Object 311.2.0076)
    - [Silver glitter masked wrestler], undated (Box 42, Object 311.2.0077)
    - [Striped silver masked wrestler], undated (Box 42, Object 311.2.0078)
    - [Black glitter masked wrestler], undated (Box 42, Object 311.2.0079)
    - [Pink glitter masked wrestler], undated (Box 42, Object 311.2.0080)
    - [Skeleton shrink wrapped], undated (Box 42, Object 311.2.0081)
    - [Grim reaper shrink wrapped], undated (Box 42, Object 311.2.0082)
    - [Female devil figurine], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0083)
    - [Male devil figurine], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0084)
    - [Plastic skeleton figurine], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0085)
    - [Wrestler figurine black with yellow cape], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0086)
    - [Wrestler figurine grey with black cape], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0087)
    - [Wrestler figurine black], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0088)
    - [Wrestler figurine blue], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0089)
    - [Wrestler figurine white pants], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0090)
    - [Wrestler figurine green pants], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0091)
    - [Wrestler figurine yellow pants], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0092)
    - [Wrestler figurine orange pants], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0093)
    - [Wrestler figurine pink pants], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0094)
    - [Wrestler figurine blue pants], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0095)
    - [Gold tinsel], undated (Box 43, Object 311.2.0096)
    - [Sugar sculpture], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0097)
    - [Skull string necklace], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0098)
    - [Resin disc], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0099)
    - [Bottle of fragrance oil], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0100)
    - [Vial of sand and shells], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0101)
    - [Santa Muerte cloth necklace], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0102)
    - [Wooden scythe], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0103)
    - [Rosary necklace], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0104)
    - [Pearl and crystal necklace], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0105)
    - [Pendant on cord necklace], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0106)
    - [Plastic grapes], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0107)
    - [Rock fragment], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0108)
    - [Blue glass pebble], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0109)
    - [Felt with skeleton embroidery], undated (Box 44, Object 311.2.0110)
    - [Painting on metal], undated (Box 45, Object 311.2.0111)